{
    "subject": "resource/Jim_Allen_(playwright)",
    "predicate": "ontology/notableWork",
    "object": "resource/Land_and_Freedom",
    "human_readable": "Jim Allen (playwright) is known for his notable work 'Land and Freedom'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9069756865501404,
            "question": "What type of work did Jim Allen create titled 'Land and Freedom'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9039832949638367,
            "question": "Is Jim Allen a playwright?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8926403522491455,
            "question": "What is the title of Jim Allen's notable work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8924676775932312,
            "question": "Name a famous play by Jim Allen."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8366594910621643,
            "question": "What is Jim Allen known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7849276661872864,
            "question": "Besides 'Land and Freedom', what other works are by Jim Allen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6943942308425903,
            "question": "Who wrote the play 'Land and Freedom'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6911600232124329,
            "question": "Jim Allen is known for his writing in which genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4658476412296295,
            "question": "Who might have acted in 'Land and Freedom'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31121528148651123,
            "question": "What themes might be explored in 'Land and Freedom'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jim Allen (playwright) is known for his notable work 'Land and Freedom'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8179_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who might have acted in 'Land and Freedom'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8179_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jim Allen is known for his writing in which genre?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8179_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who wrote the play 'Land and Freedom'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8179_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8179_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8179_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8179_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8179_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8179_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8179_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8179_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8179_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8179_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8179_31.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents provided contain information about Jim Allen, a socialist playwright, and his collaboration with Ken Loach on a film called \"Land and Freedom\", which is described as a fitting testament to Allen's work."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Jim Allen (playwright) is known for his notable work 'Land and Freedom'.\" Specifically, the document at path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8179/re-ranker-msmarco/24.txt` mentions Jim Allen's final collaboration with Ken Loach as \"Land and Freedom,\" describing it as a film that stands as a fitting testimonial to Allen."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}